Guide to the Women in Communications, Inc. (WICI) Records MC.89
New York University Archives
Women in Communications, Inc. (WICI) Records
1918-1985
1955-1984
New York University Archives
Women in Communications, inc.
MC.89
14.5 Linear Feet in 32 manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, 1 oversized flat box, 1 folder in shared oversized box, and 1 shared audiocassette box
2 videocassettes (u-matic)
2 sound tape reels
13 audiocassettes
Founded in 1929 as Theta Sigma Phi, Women in Communications, Inc. (WICI) was a professional organization for female communications professionals. After becoming the Association for Women in Communications (AWC) in 1996, the New York chapter separated and became the New York Women in Communications, Inc. (NYWICI). WICI had members in a variety of communications disciplines, such as journalism, publishing, public relations, and many more; it aimed to support and empower women in the communications field. The Women in Communications, Inc. Records consist of materials created and collected by WICI and NYWICI from 1918-1985. Materials include membership files, board of directors and executive committee meeting minutes and agendas, Matrix Award programs and photographs, conference programs, event flyers, and event audio and video recordings. All of the materials reflect the organization's mission of supporting women at different career stages and providing professional development opportunities.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Materials found in collection; provenance is unknown. A deed of gift for this collection was signed in November 2022, by Georgia Galanoudis, President-Elect of the New York Women in Communications Board of Directors.
Arrangement
The records have been arranged into six series; the series arrangement is as follows:
I. Administrative Materials
II. Events and Programs
III. Governing Bodies
IV. Matrix Awards
V. Membership
VI. Publications
All of the series are arranged chronologically.
Historical Note
In 1929, Theta Sigma Phi, the first female branch of the journalism fraternity, was founded in order to obtain equal pay to the males in the profession. In 1972, the organization was renamed Women in Communications, Inc. (WICI); WICI then became the Association for Women in Communications (AWC) in 1996. In 1998, the New York chapter, which had been very active, separated from the national organization and became New York Women in Communications, Inc. (NYWICI). New York Women in Communications is a professional organization for female communications professionals with a mission of supporting women at every career stage, fighting for equal pay, and encouraging women to speak up. WICI had a similar mission, to "keep its members prepared to meet the challenges of the rapidly developing communications profession," as noted in a brochure from 1976. WICI had members in a variety of communications disciplines (which NYWICI continues to have) including journalism, broadcasting, publishing, advertising, integrated marketing, photography, public relations, graphic design, and more. Since 1971, first WICI and now NYWICI, has honored leaders in the industry with the Matrix Award, and each year, the organization awards scholarships and grants to high school seniors, college and graduate students, and women looking for career changes.
Source cited:
NYWICI. "Our History." Accessed July 5, 2023. https://nywici.org/about/history/.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact New York University Archives, special.collections@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596, with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Scope and Contents
The Women in Communications, Inc. (WICI) Records consist of materials created and collected by WICI and NYWICI from 1918-1985. Materials cover the organization's inception as the New York chapter of Theta Sigma Phi and its evolution to the Women in Communications, Inc. (WICI) in 1972. Materials in this collection encompass the national organization and the New York chapter prior to the formation of NYWICI as a discrete organization. A majority of the collection, however, focuses on the New York chapter of WICI. Materials include administrative matters (general correspondence and financial documents), events and programs (printed matter and correspondence for luncheons, workshops, and conferences), governing bodies (correspondence and memos, meeting agendas and minutes, and elections of members of the board of directors, executive committee, and other committees), the Matrix Awards (photographs, invitations and programs, correspondence, committee materials, and nominations), membership files (mailings and correspondence), and publications such as newsletters and membership directories. Other chapters, such as Boston and Philadelphia, are represented sparsely. All of the materials reflect the organization's mission of supporting women at different career stages and providing professional development opportunities.
Women in mass media.; Women journalists -- United States; Women in the advertising industry; Women in the broadcasting industry; Women publishers; Women public relations personnel; Women's rights -- United States.; Equal pay for equal work
- Series I. Administrative Materials, 1955-1984; 1.75 Linear Feet in 4 manuscript boxes
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of administrative materials, such as stationery, award certificates, general correspondence, presidential correspondence, and financial documents (budgets and membership dues), for both WICI and NYWICI. Most of the presidential correspondence is to and from the president of NYWICI, and some of it includes correspondence to and from the national organization. Topics in the correspondence include recruitment of potential members; queries on scholarships; conferences and events by other organizations; and inquiries by the organization asking individuals to participate in events, such as delivering the keynote address at the Matrix Awards.
  - Stationery, 1955-1980 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Certificates, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1948-1959 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1964-1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
  - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 4-5)
  - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
  - Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Financial Records, 1956-1962 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Financial Records, 1967-1972 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Financial Records, 1973-1978 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Financial Records, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Financial Records, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Financial Records, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
  - Financial Records, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Series II. Events and Programs, 1951-1985; 2.62 Linear Feet in 6 manuscript boxes; 1 sound tape reels; 2 videocassettes (u-matic); 13 audiocassettes
  This series consists of materials related to various luncheons, workshops, seminars, and conferences sponsored by WICI and NYWICI. Workshops such as Career Night, conference sessions such as "Opportunities for Women Journalists: Are the Doors Locked?" (from the 1960 National Convention in Colorado Springs), and awards and fellowships that support students and those new to the profession, reflect the organization's goal of providing professional development and networking opportunities. These materials include printed matter (flyers, invitations, and programs), photographs, audio and video recordings, correspondence, news clippings and articles, and planning files (guest lists and service orders). In addition, there are statements on various issues supported by WICI and NYWICI, such as the Equal Rights Amendment and freedom of information. Programs of note include luncheon lectures by Barbara Bush, Diane Sawyer, and Jane Pauley, 1982-1983, among many others.
  - Resolution on William Oatis, September 1951 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - First Eastern Regional Convention -- Philadelphia, November 1951 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Theta Sigma Phi Travel, 1952-1955 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Hospitalized Veterans' Writing Project (HVWP), 1952-1980 (Box 4, Folder 7-8)
  - 44th National Convention -- Indianapolis, June 1953 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Student Loan Fund, 1954-1959 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Events and Programs -- General, 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Tax Research Project, 1956-1960 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Events and Programs -- General, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - National Convention -- Des Moines, June 1958 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Events and Programs -- General, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - 50th Anniversary National Convention -- Seattle, August 1959 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - High School Headliner Award, 1959-1962 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Career Award (Formerly, Student Loan Fund), 1959-1962 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Events and Programs -- General, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - National Convention -- Colorado Springs, June 1960 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Events and Programs -- General, 1960-1961 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - National Convention -- University of Kansas, June 1961 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Events and Programs -- General, 1962-1969 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - 60th Anniversary Annual National Meeting -- Austin, August 1969 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Events and Programs -- General, 1970-1973 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Annual National Meeting -- Philadelphia, October 1974 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Events and Programs -- General, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Events and Programs -- General, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Annual National Meeting -- Milwaukee, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Events and Programs -- General, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - New York State Women's Conference -- International Women's Year, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Annual National Meeting -- Honolulu, October 1977 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Events and Programs -- General, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 6, Box 33, Audiocassette 89.0007)
  - Northeastern Regional Meeting -- New York City, April 1978 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Clarion Awards, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Annual National Meeting -- Detroit, October 1978 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Events and Programs -- General, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Unidentified Events and Programs -- Photographs, circa 1978-1982 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Northeastern Regional Meeting -- Rochester, New York, April 1979 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Annual National Meeting -- Dallas, September 1979 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Events and Programs -- General, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Northeast Regional Meeting -- Philadelphia, May 1980 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Annual National Meeting -- San Diego, October 1980 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Events and Programs -- General, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 6, Box Shared University Archives 079, Quarter inch audio reel 89.0001)
  - Freedom of Information (FOI) Programs, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 7, Box 33, U-matic 89.0004)
  - Northeast Regional Meeting -- Stamford, Connecticut, April-May 1981 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Annual National Meeting, May 1981 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Events and Programs -- General, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 10-11)
  - Northeast Regional Conference -- Boston, May 1982 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - "Illiteracy in America" -- Luncheon with Barbara Bush, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 2, Box 33, Audiocassette 89.0005)
  - PRO/CON National Professional Conference -- Denver, September-October 1982 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - "The New American Woman" Panel Discussion Co-Sponsored by House Beautiful, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Events and Programs -- General, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 5-6, Box Shared University Archives 098, Audiocassette 89.0015)
  - Career Night, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 7, Box 33, Audiocassette 89.0010, Box Shared University Archives 098, Audiocassette 89.0013 and 89.0016)
  - "Libel and the First Amendment" -- Freedom of Information Panel, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 1, Box 33, Audiocassette 89.0008)
  - PRO/CON National Professional Conference -- Philadelphia, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Events and Programs -- General, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 3-4, Box 33, Audiocassette 89.0006, 89.0009, and 89.0011-89.0012, Box Shared University Archives 098, Audiocassette 89.0014 and 89.0017)
  - "60 Outstanding Members" Awards, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Events and Programs -- General, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Interviews with Marlene Sanders and Kay Lockridge, undated (Box 33, U-matic 89.0003)
- Series III. Governing Bodies, 1949-1984; 4.38 Linear Feet in 10 manuscript boxes
  Arrangement
  Arranged chronologically, first by Board of Directors and Executive Committee materials, then by committee materials.
  This series includes materials from the governing bodies of WICI and NYWICI (Board of Directors, Executive Committee, and other committees, such as the Publicity Committee and Membership Committee, among others). Materials consist of meeting minutes and agendas, election materials, and correspondence. Also included are documents related to by-laws revisions and constitutions. Materials from the national organization and the New York chapter are filed together; in a few files, other chapters are represented (for example, materials on the Los Angeles chapter are filed with the 1959 folder). Topics covered include updates and reports on upcoming and past events, committee reports, membership updates, and board and committee nominations.
  - Meeting Minutes, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1953-1956 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Meeting Minutes and Reports, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Meeting Minutes and Reports, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Meeting Minutes, Reports, and By-Laws Revisions, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Meeting Minutes, By-Laws Revisions, and Correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Meeting Minutes, By-Laws Revisions, and Correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Meeting Minutes and Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Meeting Minutes, By-Laws Revisions, and Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Meeting Minutes, By-Laws Revisions, Reports, and Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Meeting Minutes, By-Laws Revisions, and Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Meeting Minutes, By-Laws Revisions, and Correspondence, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Meeting Minutes, By-Laws Revisions, Reports, and Correspondence, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 4-5)
  - Meeting Minutes, By-Laws Revisions, and Correspondence, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 6, Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Meeting Minutes, Reports, and By-Laws Revisions, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 2-3)
  - Meeting Minutes, Reports, and By-Laws Revisions, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Meeting Minutes, Reports, and By-Laws Revisions, January-May 1981 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Meeting Minutes, Reports, and By-Laws Revisions, June 1981 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Meeting Minutes and Reports, July 1981 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Meeting Minutes and Reports, August 1981 (Box 13, Folder 3-4)
  - Meeting Minutes and Reports, September 1981 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Meeting Minutes, Reports, and By-Laws Revisions, October-November 1981 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Meeting Minutes, Reports, and By-Laws Revisions, December 1981 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Meeting Minutes, Reports, and Correspondence, January 1982 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Meeting Minutes, Reports, and Correspondence, February-March 1982 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Meeting Minutes, Reports, and Correspondence, April 1982 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Meeting Minutes, Reports, and Correspondence, May-June 1982 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Meeting Minutes, Reports, and Correspondence, July 1982 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Meeting Minutes, Reports, and Correspondence, August 1982 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Meeting Minutes and Reports, September 1982 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Meeting Minutes and Reports, October 1982 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Meeting Minutes and Reports, November 1982 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Meeting Minutes and Reports, December 1982 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Meeting Minutes and Reports, January 1983 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Meeting Minutes and Reports, February 1983 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Meeting Minutes and Reports, March 1983 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Meeting Minutes and Reports, April 1983 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Meeting Minutes and Reports, May-June 1983 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Meeting Minutes and Reports, July-September 1983 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Meeting Minutes and Reports, October-December 1983 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Meeting Minutes and Reports, January-May 1984 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Lists of Committee Members, 1977-1983 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Committee for Journalism Recruitment, 1959-1960 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Constitution Committee, 1954-1960 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Equal Rights Amendment (ERA) Task Force, 1980-1981 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Financial Advisory Committee, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Hospitality Committee, 1955-1960 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Jo Caldwell Meyer Research Grant Committee, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Job Information Committee, 1956-1982 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Juvenile Improvement Committee, 1954-1962 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Kits for Chapter Presidents, 1976-1979 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Membership Committee, 1976-1982 (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
  - Nominations Committee, 1954-1978 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Professional Chair Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Programs Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Progress of Women in Communication (POWIC) Committee, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Publicity Committee, 1956-1982 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Regional Meeting Planning Committee (New York Chapter), 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Special Projects Committee, 1958-1959 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Series IV. Matrix Awards, 1950-1984; 2.90 Linear Feet in 6 manuscript boxes and 1 oversized flat box; 1 sound tape reels
  This series consists of materials related to the Matrix Awards, which honor women who have made a difference in the field of communications and are recognized as leaders in the profession. Begun by Theta Sigma Phi as a celebration that bestowed Honor Awards to female leaders in the fields of newspapers, magazines, radio, television, public relations, and advertising, the event became the Matrix Awards in 1970. Materials include photographs, printed matter (invitations and programs), correspondence, committee materials (lists of nominees and correspondence), budgets, an audio recording, press releases, and clippings. Some chapters outside of New York had their own Matrix celebrations, which are included here.
  - Matrix Table Dinner, 1950-1951 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Matrix Table Dinner, 1952 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Matrix Table Dinner/Tea/Breakfast, 1953-1955 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Matrix Tea/Celebration, 1956-1957 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Matrix Celebration, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Matrix Celebration, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Matrix Celebration, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Matrix Celebration, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Matrix Celebration, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Matrix Celebration, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Matrix Celebration -- Invitation Only, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Matrix Celebration -- Invitation Only, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Matrix Awards -- Winners' List, 1970-1981 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Matrix Awards -- Invitation Only, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Matrix Awards, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Matrix Awards, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Matrix Awards, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Matrix Awards, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 3-4)
  - Matrix Awards, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 5-6)
  - Matrix Awards, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 1-6, Box 34)
  - Matrix Awards, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 1-4, Box 33, Quarter inch audio reel 89.0002)
  - Matrix Awards, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 5, Box 23, Folder 1-2)
  - Matrix Awards, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 3-4)
  - Matrix Awards, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Matrix Awards, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Series V. Membership, 1948-1984; 0.44 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box
  This series contains materials related to members of WICI and NYWICI, such as membership questionnaires, handbooks, statistics, membership applications, and correspondence. Also included are materials on the development of student chapters in New York universities and colleges, including New York University.
  - "Information Kit for Matrix Milestones" -- 39th Anniversary of Theta Sigma Phi, circa 1948 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Initiation Service of Theta Sigma Phi, circa 1955-1967 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Theta Sigma Phi Membership Manuals, 1956-1972 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Membership Forms and Dues Information, circa 1956-1983 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - New York Women in Communications, Inc. (NYWICI) Student Chapters, 1976-1980 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Membership Correspondence, 1958-1983 (Box 24, Folder 6-7)
  - National Membership Professional Manual, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - NYWICI Membership Questionnaires, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - NYWICI Membership Reports, 1981-1984 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Series VI. Publications, 1918-1985; 3.29 Linear Feet in 8 manuscript boxes
  Arranged first chronologically, then alphabetically beginning with Matrix Magazine.
  This series contains WICI and NYWICI publications that were a benefit of membership. Publications include Matrix Magazine, national and NYWICI newsletters, PRO/COMM: The Professional Communicator, and Career Forum. National issues of newsletters and membership directories appear before the issues of the New York chapter. Additionally, there are some newsletters from other chapters, such as Boston, Philadelphia, and Washington, D.C. Not all of the publications, such as Matrix Magazine, include complete runs of issues. Also included are the one-time publication, None But the Best: A History of Theta Sigma Phi (circa 1949); brochures; publications with seemingly shorter life spans, such as Leadership Bulletin and Job Information Bulletin; and publication guidelines from the national office. Newsletters cover such topics as individual spotlights, conference reports, by-laws changes, and award winners. Matrix Magazine includes more scholarly articles, on such subjects as the importance of using oral histories to record the past, the widening wage gap, and new technology.
  - None But the Best: A History of Theta Sigma Phi, circa 1949 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Brochures, Price Lists, and Rate Cards, 1951-1980 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Constitution and By-Laws of Theta Sigma Phi, 1956-1966 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Women in Communications, Inc. (WICI) Publications Guidelines, circa 1973 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - WICI Leadership Bulletin, 1973-1984 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - WICI Job Information Bulletin, 1978-1980 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - NYWICI Career Forum, 1980-1982 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - The Matrix, 1918 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Matrix Magazine, 1958-1968 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Matrix Magazine, 1969-1971 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Matrix Magazine, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Matrix Magazine, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Matrix Magazine, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Matrix Magazine, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Matrix Magazine, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Matrix Magazine, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Matrix Magazine, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Matrix Magazine, 1980-1981 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Theta Sigma Phi Directory of Members, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Theta Sigma Phi Directory of Members, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Theta Sigma Phi National Directory of Professional Members, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - WICI Supplemental National Directory of Professional Members, 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - WICI National Membership Directory, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 1)